Sheet Music Collection
Sheet Music Collection
- Sheet music
  - Well-known composers
    - Tchaikovsky, Pyotr Ilyich Symphonie pathétique (Op. 74), (orchestral sheet music) (signed by T. M. Osborne) (Oversize 5)
    - Verdi, Giuseppe La Traviata: opera di Verdi: I pezzi più favorite ridotti per Chitarra sola da Benedetto Razzetti (Op. 47), arr. Benedetto Razzetti, guitar (solo) (signed by W. P. Graham – William P. Graham, chancellor of SU from 1937-1942) (Oversize 5)
    - Verdi, Giuseppe Il lacerate spirito, from Simon Boccagneri., vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (baritone, bass) two copies (Oversize 5)
    - Verdi, Giuseppe Mira, di acerbe lagrime (Witness these tears of agony) from Il Trovatore, vocal (duet) (soprano, baritone or bass) (Oversize 5)
    - Von Suppé, Franz Ouvertüre zu Oper: "Zehn Mädchen und kein Mann", piano trio (piano, violin, cello) (Oversize 5)
    - Von Suppé, Franz Ouverture zur Oper: "Die Schöne Galathè" von F. v. Suppé, Bearbeitet von G. Wiehtl piano trio (piano, violin, cello) (Bearbeitet may mean "treated," "revised") (Oversize 5)
    - Wagner, Richard Hail, bright abode (March and Chorus from Tannhäuser), vocal (choral), G. Schirmer's Octavo Choruses for Mixed Voices, black cover, signed "T. M. Osborne, Director" (Oversize 5)
    - Wagner, Richard Hail, bright abode (March and Chorus from Tannhäuser), vocal (choral), G. Schirmer's Octavo Collection of Choruses, two copies (Oversize 5)
    - Wagner, Richard Hail, bright abode (March and Chorus from Tannhäuser), vocal (choral), G. Schiermer's Collection of Operatic Choruses (Oversize 5)
    - Wagner, Richard Hail, bright abode (March and Chorus from Tannhäuser), vocal (choral), G. Schiermer's Octavo Choruses for Mixed Voices, green cover, two copies (Oversize 5)
    - Wagner, Richard "Faithful and True" (Bridal Chorus from "Lohengrin"), arr. by M. Vogrich, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) two copies (basic cover) (Oversize 5)
    - Wagner, Richard "Faithful and True" (Bridal Chorus from "Lohengrin"), arr. by M. Vogrich, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) two copies (intricate cover), one signed "T. M. Osborne, Director" (Oversize 5)
    - Wagner, Richard Choral from Meistersinger (Awake, Awake), translation by J. P. Jackson, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) two copies (Oversize 5)
    - Wagner, Richard Pilgrim's Chorus (Tannhäuser), piano (solo) (Oversize 5)
    - Wagner, Richard Das Liebesmahl der Apostel: eine biblische Scene für Männerstimmen u. grosses Orchester geschrieben und Frau Charlotte Emilie Weintlig der Wittwe seines unvergesslichen Lebrers gewidmet von Richard Wagner, piano (four hands) (signed by "T. M. O.") (Oversize 5)
    - Wagner, Richard Eine Faust-Ouverture für grosses Orchester, piano (four hands) (Oversize 5)
    - Wagner, Richard Parsifal: Ein Bühnenmeihfestspiel, arr. E. Humperdink, piano (four hands) (signed "T. M. Osborne" "Sept. 1883") (Oversize 5)
    - Wagner, Richard Siegfried-Idyll, arr. Jos. Rubinstein, piano (four hands) (signed "T. M. Osborne" "July 1883") (Oversize 5)
    - Weber, Carl Mario von Ouvertüre zu "Freischütz" für Pianoforte zu 2 Händen, piano (solo) (Oversize 5)
    - Weber, Carl Maria von Jubel: Ouverture von C. M. von Weber, arr. von C. Burchard piano trio (piano, violin, cello) (Oversize 5)
  - Lesser-known composers
    - Abbott, C. B. Christy's Polka: as danced by C. N. Christy & T. Vaughn of the original Christy's Minstrels, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 5)
    - Abbott, Jane Bingham Songs by Jane Bingham Abbott: Just for To-Day, "poem has been authentically traced to Miss Sibyl F. Partridge, Liverpool, England," vocal (song) (signed by Winifred Seely Myers) (Oversize 5)
    - Abt, Franz Serenade, edited by Charles Denbigh, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) (soprano) (Oversize 5)
    - Adam, Adolphe Cantique de Nöel (Christmas Song), vocal (song with keyboard, violin or flute or cello) (soprano) (Oversize 5)
    - Adam, Adolphe Christmas Song: O Holy Night (Cantique de Nöel), obligato for Violin or ‘Cello by Henry S. Sawyer, vocal (song with piano and violin accompaniment) (Oversize 5)
    - Adam, Adolphe O Holy Night: Cantique de Nöel (Christmas Song), by James C. Warhurtst, vocal (choral with organ accompaniment) (women's voices) (Oversize 5)
    - Adams, Stephen Nancy Lee, words by Fred. E. Weatherly, M. A., vocal (song) (signed "Jennie Lee Butler" "from Booth") (Oversize 5)
    - Adams, Stephen The Holy City: Song with Organ Accompaniment, the words by F. E. Weatherly, the music by Stephen Adams, vocal (song with organ accompaniment) (low voice) two copies (Oversize 5)
    - Aidé, H. The Call of the Flag, (orchestral sheet music), two set copies (Oversize 5)
    - Albert, L. "Rose Dreams" (valse pensive), keyboard (solo) (Oversize 5)
    - Alberti, H. Zulu-Marsch (Op. 71), (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 5)
    - Alpert, S. L. The Hurricane: March-Twostep, arranged by E. T. Paull, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 5)
    - Ambrose, Paul The Lord Is My Light, vocal (duet) (soprano, tenor) (Oversize 5)
    - Andrews, John C. Somebody's Coming but I'll Not Tell Who: sung with great applause by Miss Jane A. Andrews, Dedicated to Miss Eveline Hayner, vocal (song) (signed by Phillie A. Stover) (Oversize 5)
    - Apelles United States Military Academy: Song of the Graduates, 1852, words by a Cadet, vocal (song) (facsimile copy) (Oversize 5)
    - Arne, Thomas Augustine Where the Bee Sucks, words by William Shakespere (sic, should read "Shakespeare") (from The Tempest Act V Scene I), edited and arranged by Charles Vincent, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 5)
    - Ascher, Joseph La vaillance, polka militaire, piano (solo) (signed "Jennie Lee Butler" "Hanover, Va.") (Oversize 5)
    - Ashford, E. L. My Task, vocal (duet) (soprano, tenor) (Oversize 5)
    - Auber The Laughing Song, from Auber's Manon Lescaut, arranged by Anne Seguin, vocal (song) (Oversize 5)
    - Aubert, V. B. Pensée Celeste, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 5)
    - Aulin, Tor Fyra Aquareller, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 5)
    - Baker, Fred T. Danse Ecossais, piano (four hands) (signed "Katherine Estelle Shipht" "Rockla of College" "Nyack… Hudson"—difficult to read) (Oversize 5)
    - Baker, Thomas The Flowers are Sleeping: Ballad sung by Mad'lle Anna Zerr, dedicated to Mrs. Charles St. John, words by J. W. Lake, vocal (song) (Oversize 5)
    - Balfe, M. W. I dreamt I dwelt in Marble Halls, from Bohemian Girl, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (signed "Miss Jennie Butler" "BGFS") (Oversize 5)
    - Balfe, M. W. The Light of Other Days: Sung by Mr. Brough, vocal (song) (Oversize 5)
    - Ball, Ernest R. Dear Little Boy of Mine, lyric by J. Keirn Brennan, vocal (song) (high voice) (Oversize 5)
    - Ball, Ernest R. My Hour, lyric by Gordon Johnstone, vocal (song) (high voice) (Oversize 5)
    - Barker, G. Haunted Stream, vocal (song) (signed "Miss Jennie L. Butler" "BGFS") (Oversize 5)
    - Barthélemen, R. Caressing Butterfly, arr. for orchestra by Otto Langey (orchestral sheet music) (marked "incomplete") (Oversize 5)
    - Bartlett, Homer N. O Lord, Be Merciful (Op. 96), vocal (song with organ accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 5)
    - Bartlett, J. C. Sleep, My Jesu: Cradle Hymn of the Virgin, words by Abbie F. Judd, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (medium voice) (Oversize 5)
    - Beach, H. H. A. Three Shakespeare Songs set to Music No. 3: Fairy Lullaby (Op. 37), (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 5)
    - Bellak, James The Star Sett: a Collection of One Hundred beautiful melodies, arranged by James Bellak: Beatrice di Tenda: Star Set no. 36 (Op. 1501), piano (solo) (Oversize 5)
    - Bellak, James 20 Charms, for the Piano-forte, by J. Bellak: No. 7: Carnival of Venice (Op. 325), piano (solo) (Oversize 5)
    - Bellak, James Floral Set for piano by James Bellak: No. 18: En avant march, piano (solo) (Oversize 5)
    - Bemberg, H. The Song of Kisses/La Chanson des Baisers, English version by R. H. Elkin, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) two copies (Oversize 5)
    - Benatzky, Ralph Im "Weissen Rössl" am Wolfgangsee… Lied und Marsch aus Charells "Im weissen Rössl", Text by Robert Gilbert, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) two copies (Oversize 5)
    - Bergé, Irénée Dramatic Reproach (Depicting Dramatic Emotion), orchestration by Sol P Levy (orchestral sheet music) (title covered and re-labeled "After the Fight" and "I Know You're a Stool Pigeon") (Oversize 5)
    - Bertrand-Brown Maybe, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 5)
    - Berwald, W. O Save Me, God, vocal (song with organ accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 5)
    - Bevan, Frederick Our Father, words by F. E. Weatherly, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 5)
    - Blessner, Gustave Oh! Ever Think of Me: a Swiss Melody, written by Miss E. Pickering & sung with great applause by Miss Richings at her concerts, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 5)
    - Blumenthal, Jacques Across the Far Blue Hills, Marie, words by Fred E. Weatherly, vocal (song) (Oversize 5)
    - Bohm, C. Fairy Revels (Fantasie), piano (solo) (Oversize 5)
    - Borch, Gaston Impish Elves, (orchestral sheet music) (title covered up, replaced with "The Refuge") (Oversize 5)
    - Boyd, Jeanne M. In Italy, words by Schwarmel Iris, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (signed "WMyers") (high voice) (Oversize 5)
    - Brahe, May H. I Passed by Your Window, words by Helen Taylor, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 5)
    - Branscombe, Gena A Lovely Maiden Roaming: Song from "The Lute of Jade" Song Cycle, translated from the Chinese by L. Cramner-Byng, vocal (song) (soprano, tenor) (Oversize 5)
    - Briggs, C. S. Hold Thou My Hand, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (medium voice) (Oversize 5)
    - Briggs, C. S. Hold Thou My Hand, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 5)
    - Brockway, Howard Sonate für Violine und Pianoforte (Op. 9), (violin and piano) (Oversize 5)
    - Brown, A. Seymour Can't You See I Love You? From The Newlyweds and Their baby, lyrics and music also by Nat. D. Ayer, and John W. Bratton, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 5)
    - Brownell, Leila M. Four Leaf Clover, words by Ella Higginson, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice with violin obligato) (Oversize 5)
    - Buck, Dudley The Lord Is My Light, vocal (duet with organ or piano accompaniment) (soprano and tenor) two copies (Oversize 6)
    - Buck, Dudley The Night Song of Bethlehem: "Et in terra pax hominibus bonae voluntatis", vocal (song with piano or organ accompaniment) (high voice) two copies (Oversize 6)
    - Buck, Dudley O Saviour of the World, vocal (song with organ accompaniment) (high voice) two copies, both signed by Winifred S. Myers (Oversize 6)
    - Burgmein, J. Esquisses au Crayon par J. Burgmein: Trois morceaux caracteristiques pour piano, piano (four hands) (3 pieces kept together) (signed "T. M. Osborne" "July 1883") (Oversize 6)
    - Burnett, Earl Leave Me With a Smile, also by Chas. Koehler, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 6)
    - Buzzi-Pecca, A. Gloria, words by M. C. Schuyler, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (signed "WMyers") (Oversize 6)
    - Cadman, Charles Wakefield The Doe-Skin Blanket (Op. 66), words by Cecil Fanning, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 6)
    - Cadman, Charles Wakefield The Lyric Rose of Love: The Legend of Venus and Adonis, words by Doris Smith, vocal (song) (Oversize 6)
    - Cadman, Charles Wakefield My Gift for You, words by Grace Osburn Wharton, vocal (duet with piano accompaniment) (soprano and tenor) (Oversize 6)
    - Cadman, Charles Wakefield Prairie Night, words by Grace Osburn Wharton, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 6)
    - Caldara, Anton Come raggio di sol/As on the swelling wave, English version by Dr. Th. Baker, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 6)
    - Calegari, F. Il Dilettante di Chitarra: pezzi d'Opere teatrali: Libro II (Complete), also transcritti in modo facile per chitarra sola da L. G. Rossi, guitar (solo) (signed by W. P. Graham) (Oversize 6)
    - Camp, John S. Calm on the List'ning Ear of Night, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (tenor, soprano) (Oversize 6)
    - Campana, F. Guard ache Bianca luna/See the Pale Moon, vocal (duet with piano accompaniment) (soprano and alto, tenor and bass) two copies (Oversize 6)
    - Campbell-Tipton A Spirit Flower, words by B. Martin Stanton, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 6)
    - Cano, D. A. Bolero en la Opera Las Visperas Sicilianas, puesto para Guitarra, guitar (solo) (Oversize 6)
    - Capitani, G. C. Illusioni: Grand Valse, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 6)
    - Carleton, Bob Ja Da (Ja Da, Ja Da, Jing Jing Jing!), vocal (song) (Oversize 6)
    - Cassard, Cora Haunt of the Witches, vocal (song) (Oversize 6)
    - Catlin, E. N. Polo Galop (Op. 71), (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 6)
    - Cave, J. H. They Have Decked Her for the Bridal: a popular ballad, Poetry by Henry Abrahams, Esq., vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 6)
    - Chapuis, Auguste Pastoral/Pastorale, words by Armand Lafrique, English version by M. Louise Baum, accompaniment by Arthur H. Ryder, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) (women's voices) three copies (Oversize 6)
    - Charpentier, Gustave "E'er since the day when unto the I gave me" from Louise, a Musical Romance, English translation by Henry Grafton Chapman, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 6)
    - Chassaigne, F. Gems from Falka, a Comic Opera by M. M. Leterrier and Vanloo, English version by H. B. Farnie, vocal (songs with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 6)
    - Chassaigne, F. Gems from Nadjy, libretto by Alfred Murray, vocal (songs) two copies (Oversize 6)
    - Christy, E. P. Old Folks at Home: Ethiopian Melody, as sung by Christy's Minstrels, vocal (song) (facsimile copy) (Oversize 6)
    - Clark, Ella Southworth The March of the Partiots, vocal (solo, duet, or quartette chorus) (Oversize 6)
    - Clay, Frederic I'll Sing Thee Songs of Araby, words by W. G. Wills, arranged by W. Franke Harling, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 6)
    - Clayton, C. The Bachelor's Lament, words by Caroline, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 6)
    - Clough-Leiter, H. My Lady Chlo (Negro Love-Song) (Op. 5), words by Myron V. Freese, vocal (chorus with piano accompaniment) (two copies) (Oversize 6)
    - Cobb, A. T. Easter Carol, vocal (song) (marked "Complimentary") (Oversize 6)
    - Comly-Barton Troupe Vocal Selections from Olivette, vocal (songs) (Oversize 6)
    - Coerne, Louis Adolphe Easter Morning (Op. 159), Text by Frederick B. Hornby, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 6)
    - Coerne, Louis Adolphe Six Vocal Duets with Pianoforte Accompaniment No. 2: The Gate of the Singing Winds, vocal (duet with piano accompaniment) (soprano and baritone) two copies (Oversize 6)
    - Cohan, George M. Good-bye, Bargravia from The Royal Vagamond, vocal (song) (Oversize 6)
    - Cook, T. J. Three Bells Polka, dedicated to Capt. Creighton, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 6)
    - Cook, James Francis Ol' Car'lina, vocal (choral with keyboard accompaniment) three copies, one signed "Boyd F. Eckroat" (Oversize 6)
    - Coombs, C. Whitney O Light of Love Divine: And Easter Song, words by Evangeline Close, vocal (song with piano or organ accompaniment) (Oversize 6)
    - Coombs, C. Whitney Star of the East: A Christmas Song, words by Bishop Heber, vocal (song with piano accompaniment and violin obligato) (soprano or tenor) two copies, one signed "Winifred Seely Myers" (Oversize 6)
    - Coombs, C. Whitney Under the Silent Stars: A Christmas Song, words by Phillips Brooks, vocal (song with piano and violin accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 6)
    - Coote, Charles Jr. Corn Flower: Valse, piano (solo) (Oversize 6)
    - Cottrau, Teodoro Santa Lucia (Over the Rippling Sea), Neapolitan barcarolle, edited by Mario Favilli, translated by Thomas Oliphant, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (signed "Property of Somerset-Y" "Syracuse University") (medium voice) (with handwritten notes on separate sheets within) (Oversize 6)
    - Cowell, Augusta The Lonely Harp: Ballad: arranged with harp accompaniment, words by The Honorable Mrs. Norton, vocal (song with harp accompaniment) (Oversize 6)
    - Cox, Ralph Aspiration: "To Build Is Joy", words by Bertye Y. Williams, vocal (song) (soprano, tenor) (Oversize 6)
    - Crosby, L. V. H. Welcome Again with Song to Greet You, Words by Marshall S. Pike, vocal (choral with keyboard accompaniment) (signed "Phillie A. Stover") (Oversize 6)
    - Curran, Pearl G. The Lord Is My Shepherd, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 6)
    - Custance, Arthur F. M. Still, still with Thee, words by Harriet Beecher Stowe, vocal (song with piano or organ accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 6)
    - D'Albert, Charles The Sontag Polka, piano (solo) (signed "Jennie Lee Butler" "Hanover, Va") (Oversize 6)
    - D'Albert, Charles Sweethearts' Waltzes, piano (solo) (Oversize 6)
    - Davis, Benny Oh How I Miss You To-Night, also by Joe Burke and Mark Fisher, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (includes ukulele accompaniment also) (Oversize 6)
    - Davis, Chas M. Blissful Name, Words by Anne Steele, vocal (duet) (soprano and alto) (Oversize 6)
    - De Lano, C. S. Miramar Waltz, guitar (solo) (Oversize 6)
    - Dempster, William R. I'm Alone, All Alone, words by Lewis F. Thomas, Esq., dedicated to Miss Abby Ball of Boston, vocal (song) (signed "Phillie A. Stover" "A. A. Riddell." "Mr. Linder" among others) (Oversize 6)
    - Dennée, Charles Vocal Gems from The Merry-Go-Round, vocal (songs) (Oversize 6)
    - Densmore, John H. In a Field, words by Harold Susman, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 6)
    - Densmore, John H. Longing, Dear, For You, vocal (song with piano accompaniment and violin or cello obbligato) (high voice) (Oversize 6)
    - Densmore, John H. Starry Night, vocal (duet with piano accompaniment) (soprano and alto) (Oversize 6)
    - Denza, Luigi Dusky Night Now Spreads / Or Che Notte, from the Italian by Nathan Haskell Dole, vocal (duet with piano accompaniment) (soprano and mezzo-soprano or tenor and baritone) two copies (Oversize 6)
    - Denza, Luigi The Girls of Seville, words by Frederic E. Weatherly, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (soprano) (Oversize 6)
    - Desenberg, Edward Kalamazoo: An Original Rag Time Cake-Walk, arr. by Andrew Luck (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 6)
    - Donaldson, Walter When You're in Love, also written and composed by Walter Blaufuss, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (optional ukulele and "banjulele banjo" accompaniment) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 6)
    - Dorel, Francis The Garden of Your Heart, words by Edward Teschemacher, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (low voice) (Oversize 6)
    - Dorn, C. J. La prière d'une vierge / The Maidens Prayer, guitar (solo) (Oversize 6)
    - Dow, Howard M. I Will Wash My Hands in Innocency, vocal (bass solo with male quartet with organ accompaniment) (stamped "Property of Tigris Temple") two copies (Oversize 6)
    - Dressler, Louis R. The Angels' Song, words by Mary Holden Willingham, music by Louis R. Dressler, vocal (song with violin obbligato) (high voice) (Oversize 6)
    - Dressler, Louis R. Christ is Risen, words by Mary LeConte Holden, vocal (song with violin obbligato) (high voice) (Oversize 6)
    - Dressler, Paul On the Banks of the Wabash, Far Away, vocal (song) (Oversize 6)
    - Dressler, W. The Lancers Quadrilles / Les Lanciers, piano (solo) (signed "Anna Hinkley" "March 25th 1874" "Please Return to Miss Milicent A. Hinkley, 187 Comstock Place, Syracuse, N.Y.") (Oversize 6)
    - Drigo, R. Colombine's Treasures / Les Trésors de Colombine: Petit air de ballet, words by Pierre d'Amor, English version by Frederick H. Martens, vocal (song) (Oversize 6)
    - Dunn, James P. Come unto Him, words by Frederick H. Martens, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 6)
    - Earl, Mary Love Bird Fox Trot, also by Ted Fiorito, arr. by George F. Briegel (orchestral sheet music) (with choral parts) (Oversize 6)
    - Edwards, Leo There's a Sunny Smile Waiting for Me, lyric by Harry D. Kerr, vocal (song) (Oversize 6)
    - Effinger, Stanley S. I Shall Not Pass Again This Way, verse by Ellen H. Underwood, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) two copies, one signed "WMyers," (Oversize 6)
    - Eichberg, Julius To Thee, O Country!: National Hymn, words by Miss Anna P. Eichberg, vocal (choral with keyboard accompaniment) (Oversize 6)
    - Ellis, Horace E. I Will Lay Me Down in Peace, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (soprano or tenor) (Oversize 6)
    - Elton, Fred The Wee Hoose' Mang the Heather, written by Harry Lauder and Gilbert Wells, also composed by Harry Lauder, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 6)
    - Emmans, George H. Barbara Fritchie March, keyboard (solo with vocal chorus) (Oversize 6)
    - Emmett, Dan D. Dixie's Land, vocal (song) (Oversize 6)
    - Emmett, Dan D. I Wish I Was in Dixie's Land, written and composed expressly for Bryant's Minstrels, arranged for the pianoforte by W. L. Hobbs, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 6)
    - Engländer, Ludwig Songs from Canary & Lederer's NY Casino Production The Passing Show, written by Sydney Rosenfeld, vocal (songs) (Oversize 6)
    - Fall, Leo Potpourri aus der Operette Madame Pompadour, piano (solo) (Oversize 7)
    - Fall, Leo Potpourri aus der Operette Die Rose von Stambul, piano (solo) (Oversize 7)
    - Faning, Eaton The Miller's Wooing, words by Julia Goddard, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Faning, Eaton Song of the Vikings, words written by Somerville Gibney, vocal (choral with keyboard accompaniment) three copies, one signed "Steward" (Oversize 7)
    - Farmer, Henry Friendly Pastime, piano (four hands) (signed "Milly A Hinkley" "July 22nd 1884") (Oversize 7)
    - Fillmore, J. H. An Easter Song, words by Palmer Hartsough, vocal (song) (Oversize 7)
    - Fisher, William Arms Every Time I Feel the Spirit: Negro Spiritual, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) two copies, one marked "Myers," one marked "Piano," one marked "Beal" (Oversize 7)
    - Foerster, Adolph M. Song to the Saviour, words by Sibella Elizabeth Miles, vocal (song with piano or organ accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 7)
    - Forte, W. L'Anima dell'Opera: Pièces favorites pour piano et flute par W. Forte No. 27: Adelaide de Beethoven, (piano, flute, and violin) (Oversize 7)
    - Forster, Dorothy Because I Love You Dear, words by Marie Seton, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 7)
    - Forster, Dorothy The Joy of Living, words by Francis Clark, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 7)
    - Franke-Harling, W. Secrets, poem by Mary M. Dodge, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) two copies (Oversize 7)
    - Freeman, Harold Girl of Mine, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 7)
    - Freeman, Harold B. Only a Rosebud, words and music also by J. Edwin Allemong, vocal (song) (Oversize 7)
    - Frey, Adolf Incline Your Ear, vocal (song with organ accompaniment) (high voice) (signed "Winifred S. Myers '16-'17") (Oversize 7)
    - Friml, Rudolf High Jinks, book and lyrics by Otto Hauerbach, vocal (song) (medium voice) (Oversize 7)
    - Friml, Rudolf When a Maid Comes Knocking at your Heart, words by Otto Hauerbach, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (Oversize 7)
    - Friml, Rudolf You're in Love!, lyric by Otto Hauerbach and Edward Clark, vocal (song) (Oversize 7)